# Ingvar

# **Nilsson**

### **Contact**

#### Address:

Alexandar 50, Toronto, Canada

#### **Email:**

champion5star247963@gmail.com

#### Skype:

live:.cid.8ad0146f263d770c

#### Skills

- React JS
- React Native
- Vue.js
- Express.js
- Laravel
- Node.js
- Javascript
- Typescript
- Python
- PHP
- MongoDB

# Language

• English C1

## **Summary**

I am a passionate senior full-stack web and cross-platform mobile engineer with 8+ years of experience delivering software from MVPs to million-user web apps. My experience span a variety of industries, including education, travel, health, and social media. I pride myself on dependable communication and high-quality deliveries.

# **Skill Highlights**

- User friendly UX/UI
- API building and Integration
- Soket IO
- Database design

# **Experience**

Front-end Developer (UX and UI) - 07/2018 to 03/2021 ITM HOUSE, Toronto, Canada

- Developed an iOS and Android app to allow students in Belgium to apply for work.
- Developed a PWA for recruiters to match with students.
- Built a continuous integration workflow to test and deploy the apps.

Senior React Developer - 07/2015 to 10/2017

NOVISMART TECH., Wien, Austria

- Worked on large-scale React apps.
- Maintained large-scale JavaScript apps.
- Created and deployed React Native apps.
- Worked closely with the product/design team.
- Reviewed and kept code quality high.

### **Education**

Bachelor of Degree in **Computer Science** - 2013 Helsinki University, Helsinki, Finland

2008 - 2013

## **Certification**

**Certified Web and Mobile Application Developer** 

Provider: SMTP Issued: January 2020